<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on My Documentations</title>
    <link>https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on My Documentations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 15:41:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Git_nginx</title>
      <link>https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/git_nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 15:41:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/git_nginx/</guid>
      <description>Push local files to NGINX using GIT #  objectives #   install git in virtual machine connect local git to VPS push local static site to VPS configure NGINX to host the site  returned error message  The requested ULR returned error: 403
on stack overflow it says 403 is a credential error. Git can only be accessed by ssh key. So we need to generate ssh key pair to connect local files to my vps with this tutorial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/nginx-config-10-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/nginx-config-10-08/</guid>
      <description>objectives #   unlink wordpress with NGINX 端口 upload static Hugo site configurate nginx 让 hugo site &amp;amp; other service占用不同端口  wordpress #  log in to server
su - author to change to the author user. Author user is for wordpress and in sudo group. Installed according to the tutorial. Database error when docker-compose. Put down first.
Upload static Hugo site #  hugo site generated. Then try to push to vps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/publish-hugo-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/publish-hugo-on-github/</guid>
      <description>Publish Hugo on Github #  objectives #   generate hugo site locally push generated site - in /public to github use github page to view the site   set github action to automatically push use git to push to my VPS host on my domain  work #  generate site locally #  To generate the site in hugo, cd in the site root, run hugo, the site will be generated in /public 目录。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/publish-hugo-on-nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yue2.github.io/notes/docs/publish-hugo-on-nginx/</guid>
      <description>Publish Static Hugo Site on VPS with NGINX #  objectives #   install git on VPS push local site to VPS using git configurate NGINX to host site   publish another site using 另一个端口，configurate NGINX certbot?  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
